Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: 1960 and Before, 1889-1963; 197990; 44 Linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Edit: 1953: Russia, 198862 (Offsite-box 420, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1954: America, 198861 (Offsite-box 420, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1954: Far East, 198860 (Offsite-box 420, Folder 29)
  - Edit: 1954: Foreign Policy Appraisal: July, 198859 (Offsite-box 420-421)
  - Edit: 1954: Foreign Policy Appraisal: Aug., 198858 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 2-3)
  - Edit: 1954: Hydrogen Bomb & Oppenheimer Case: Publicity, 198857 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 4-5)
  - Edit: 1954: Hydrogen Bomb & Oppenheimer Case: Misc, 198856 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 6-7)
  - Edit: 1954: Italy, 198855 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1954: Mideast, 198854 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1954: Misc, 198853 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 10-11)
  - Edit: 1954: Organization, 198852 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1954: World Economic Program, 198851 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1955: Far East: Jan-Apr, 198850 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1955: Far East: May-Dec, 198849 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1955: Italy, 198848 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1955: Mideast, 198847 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1955: Russia, 198846 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1955: South America, 198845 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1956: America, 198844 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1956: Cancer Cigarette Issue, 198843 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1956: Far East: China Visas For Newsmen, 198842 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1956: Far East: Misc, 198841 (Offsite-box 421, Folder 23-24)
  - Edit: 1956: Hungary, 198840 (Offsite-box 421-422)
  - Edit: 1956: Italy, 198839 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1956: Latin America, 198838 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1956: Mideast, 198837 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 4-5)
  - Edit: 1956: Organization, 198836 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1956: Russia, 198835 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1956: South America, 198834 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1956: Misc, 198833 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 9-10)
  - Edit: 1957: America, 198832 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1957: Cancer Cigarette Issue, 198831 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 12)
  - Edit: China Visas For Newsmen, 198830 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1957: Far East: Misc, 198829 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1957: Latin America, 198828 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1957: Mideast, 198827 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1957: Organization, 198826 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1957: Misc, 198825 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1958-1959: Art, 198824 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1958: America, 198823 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1958: Cancer Cigarettes, 198822 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1958: Far East: HRL'S "Special" File, 198821 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1958: Far East: Misc, 198820 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1958: Foreign Policy: Max Ways Correspondence, 198819 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1958: Foreign Policy: Max Ways Memos, 198818 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1958: Latin America, 198817 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1958: Law, 198816 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1958: Mideast, 198815 (Offsite-box 422, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1958: Organization, 198814 (Offsite-box 423)
  - Edit: 1958: Organization [RESTRICTED], 198813 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Edit: 1958: Russia, 198812 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1958: Misc, 198811 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 3-4)
  - Edit: 1959: America, 198810 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1959: Cancer Cigarette, 198809 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1959: Far East, 198808 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1959: Foreign Policy: Max Ways Book "Beyond Survival", 198807 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1959: Latin America: Bolivia, 198806 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1959: Latin America: Cuba, 198805 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 10-11)
  - Edit: 1959: Latin America: Misc, 198804 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1959: Law, 198803 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1959: Organization, 198802 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 14)
  - Edit: "Political Theory" (Special Research File for H.R.L.), 198801 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1959: Russia, 198800 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1959: Space & Missiles, 198799 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1959: Misc, 198798 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1960: America: Jan-March, 198797 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1960: America: April-June, 198796 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1960: America: July-Sept, 198795 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1960: America: Oct-Dec, 198794 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1960: Cancer Cigarette, 198793 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1960: Far East: Japanese Press Incident, 198792 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1960: Far East: Vietnam, 198791 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1960: Far East: Misc, 198790 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1960: Latin America, 198789 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1960: Law, 198788 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1960: Misc, 198787 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1960: Organization, 198786 (Offsite-box 423, Folder 29-30)
  - Editorial Services: 1941 & Before, 198785 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Services: 1942-1950, 198784 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 2)
  - Editorial Services: 1951-1960, 198783 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 3)
  - Films, 198782 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 4)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Preface, 198781 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Preface [RESTRICTED], 198780 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Misc (Undated Papers), 198779 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 6)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Board of Directors Memos, 198778 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 7)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Circulation Promotion, 198777 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 8)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Correspondence: 1928- August 1929, 198776 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 9)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Correspondence: September-December 1929, 198775 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Correspondence: September-December 1929 [RESTRICTED], 198774 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1930: Response to First Issues, 198773 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 11-12)
  - Fortune: 1930: Edit: Stories, 198772 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1930: Edit: Stories [RESTRICTED], 198771 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1930: Edit: Misc, 198770 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1930: Misc, 198769 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1931: Edit: Stories, 198768 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1931: Edit: Misc, 198767 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1931: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED], 198766 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1931: Misc, 198765 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Stories: 12/31, Branch Banking, 198764 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198763 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Misc, 198762 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Stories: Housing Series, 198761 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1932: Misc, 198760 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1933: Misc, 198759 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1933: Edit: Stories: 8/33, International Harvester, 198758 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1933: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198757 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1933: Edit: Misc, 198756 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: New Yorker, 198755 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: New Yorker [RESTRICTED], 198754 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: Jan-May, 198753 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: Jan-May [RESTRICTED], 198752 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: June-Dec, 198751 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: June-Dec [RESTRICTED], 198750 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Munitions, 198749 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Munitions [RESTRICTED], 198748 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Misc, 198747 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED], 198746 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Du Ponts, 198745 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: 12/34, Illuminated Manuscrips, 198744 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Misc, 198743 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198742 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: Misc [RESTRICTED], 198741 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 4/35, Nervous Breakdown, 198740 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 10/35, Hearst, 198739 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 10/35, Hearst [RESTRICTED], 198738 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 11/35, Campbell Soup, 198737 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Misc, 198736 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1935: Misc, 198735 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 1/36-7/36, 198734 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 1/36-7/36 [RESTRICTED], 198733 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 8/36-12/36, 198732 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 8/36-12/36 [RESTRICTED], 198731 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Misc, 198730 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 2/36, Jews in America, 198729 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 14-15)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 3/36, U.S. Steel, 198728 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 3/36, ALF Landon, 198727 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 4/36, Twin Cities, 198726 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 8/36, Small Town, Rochester, 198725 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 9/36, Japanese Issue, 198724 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1936: Misc, 198723 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Meetings, 198722 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Hodgins' Respectus, 198721 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 1/37-7/37, 198720 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 1/37-7/37 [RESTRICTED], 198719 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 9/37, Shipping, 198718 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 8/37-12/37, 198717 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 8/37-12/37 [RESTRICTED], 198716 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 12/37, University of Chicago, 198715 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 1/37, Simmons, 198714 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 3/37 Cancer, 198713 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 3/37, Background for War: Britain, 198712 (Offsite-box 425, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 4/37, Aviation Safety, 198711 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 4/37, Background for War: Spain, 198710 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 5/37, It Happened in Steel, 198709 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 5/37, Background for War: Germany, 198708 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 6/37, Background for War: France, 198707 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 7/37, Background for War: Armaments, 198706 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 8/37; Background for War: Russia, 198705 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 11/37, Industrial Warfare, 198704 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 11/37, Southern Pacific, 198703 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Misc, 198702 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1937: Misc, 198701 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Business &Government Editorials, 198700 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 2/38, Accident of Birth, 198699 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 4/38, Small Town, Oskaloosa, 198698 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 1/38-6/38, 198697 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 10/38, AMA, 198696 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Misc, 198695 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 7/38-12/38, 198694 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 19-20)
  - Fortune: 1938: Misc, 198693 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Business &Government Editorials, 198692 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 2/39, Vermont Farm, 198691 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 7/39, New York Issue, 198690 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 1/39-7/39, 198689 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 8/39-12/39, 198688 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Misc, 198687 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1939: Misc, 198686 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Stories: 6/40, Philippines, 198685 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Stories: 8/40, Hawaii, 198684 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1940: Misc, 198683 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198682 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 32-33)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 10/38, Mexico, 198681 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Misc, 198680 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 34)
  - Fortune: 1941: Edit: Stories: 3/41, Air Power Issue, 198679 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1941: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198678 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1941: Edit: Misc, 198677 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1941: Misc, 198676 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Misc, 198675 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1942: Misc, 198674 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 1/42-4/42, 198673 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 5/42-12/42, 198672 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 2/42, American Locomotives, 198671 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 2/42, Negroes and War, 198670 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 8/42, Patent Laws, 198669 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Misc, 198668 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Stories: 1/43, Air Navigation, 198667 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Stories: 1/43-6/43, 198666 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Stories: 7/43-12/43, 198665 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 15-16)
  - Fortune: 1943: Misc, 198664 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Misc, 198663 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1944: Edit: Stories: 4/44, Japan Issue, 198662 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 19-20)
  - Fortune: 1944: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198661 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 21-22)
  - Fortune: 1944: Misc, 198660 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1944: History, 198659 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Organization, 198658 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 25-26)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: 2/45, West Coast Issue, 198657 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 1-2)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: 3/45, Beardsley Ruml, 198656 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: 10/45, Sugar, 198655 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198654 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Misc, 198653 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1945: Fortnightly [empty], 198652 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1945: Misc, 198651 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1946: Edit: Misc, 198650 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1946: Edit: Stories, 198649 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1946: Misc, 198648 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Stories: 6/47-7/47: Economics, 198647 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Stories: 3/47, Coal, 198646 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 13-14)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198645 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Misc, 198644 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1947: Misc, 198643 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Directive, 198642 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1948: Response to Directive Mailing, 198641 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 1/48-2/48, 198640 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 20-21)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 3/48-4/48, 198639 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 22-23)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 5/48-8/48, 198638 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 24-25)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 9/48-12/48, 198637 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Stories, 198636 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1948: Misc, 198635 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1949: Edit: Stories: 4/49, Japanese Economic Recovery, 198634 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1949: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198633 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1949: Edit: Misc, 198632 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1949: Misc, 198631 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1950: Edit: Misc, 198630 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1950: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198629 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1950: Misc, 198628 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1950: Edit: Stories: 1/50, Made in France, Portfolio, 198627 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1951: Edit: Misc, 198626 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1951: Edit: Stories: 2/51, The Permanent Revolution, 198625 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1951: Misc, 198624 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1951: The Tycoon is Dead, 198623 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1951: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198622 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1952: Edit: Stories: 2/52, Washington Issue, 198621 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1952: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198620 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1952: Edit: Misc, 198619 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1952: Misc, 198618 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1953: Edit: Stories: 2/53, Russian Issue, 198617 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1953: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198616 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1953: Edit: Misc, 198615 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1953: Misc, 198614 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1954: Edit: Stories: 5/54, New York Central, 198613 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1954: Edit: Misc, 198612 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1954: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198611 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1954: Misc, 198610 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Anniversary Series, 198609 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Misc: 1/55-6/55, 198608 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Misc: 7/55-12/55, 198607 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 26-27)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198606 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: 12/55, Art Market, 198605 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: 2/55, Confident Twenty-Fives, 198604 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: 8/55, GSA, 198603 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1955: Misc, 198602 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 32)
  - Fortune: 1956: Edit: Misc, 198601 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1956: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198600 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1956: Edit: Stories: 3/56, National Security Council, 198599 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1956: Misc, 198598 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Misc, 198597 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: 2/57 &7/57, Russia, 198596 (Offsite-box 430)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: 2/57 &7/57, Russia [RESTRICTED], 198595 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198594 (Offsite-box 430)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: Misc [RESTRICTED], 198593 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Fortune: 1957: Misc, 198592 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Stories: 8/58, Mc Cone Arrives in Washington, 198591 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Stories: 12/58, TV: The Light That Failed, 198590 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198589 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Misc, 198588 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 12-13)
  - Fortune: 1958: Misc, 198587 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Misc, 198586 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 15-16)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Stories: 1/59 &7/59, Howard Hughes, 198585 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Stories: 12/59, Rostow-Wright Debate, 198584 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Stories: Misc, 198583 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1959: Misc, 198582 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1960: Edit: Misc, 198581 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1960: Edit: Stories, 198580 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1960: 30th Anniversary, 198579 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1960: Misc, 198578 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 24)
  - FYI [employee newsletter], 198577 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 25-26)
  - International (TLI): 1936-1944, 198576 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 27)
  - International (TLI): 1945: Jan.-Aug., 198575 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 28)
  - International (TLI): 1945: Sept.-Dec., 198574 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 29)
  - International (TLI): 1946: Jan.-June, 198573 (Offsite-box 430-431)
  - International (TLI): 1946: July-Dec., 198572 (Offsite-box 431)
  - International (TLI): 1946: July-Dec. [RESTRICTED], 198571 (Offsite-box R3)
  - International (TLI): 1947, 198570 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 3)
  - International (TLI): 1948, 198569 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 4)
  - International (TLI): 1949-1950, 198568 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 5)
  - International (TLI): 1951-1953, 198567 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 6)
  - International (TLI): 1954-1955, 198566 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 7)
  - International (TLI): 1956-1957, 198565 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 8)
  - International (TLI): 1958, 198564 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 9)
  - International (TLI): 1959, 198563 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 10)
  - International (TLI): 1960, 198562 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 11)
  - Legal Department, 198561 (Offsite-box 431)
  - Legal Department [RESTRICTED], 198560 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1935 &Before: Includes Martin Experiment, 198559 (Offsite-box 431)
  - Life: 1935 &Before: Includes Martin Experiment [RESTRICTED], 198558 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1936: Circulation Promotion, 198557 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 15-16)
  - Life: 1936: June: Prospectus --- Draft #1 ("Dime"), 198556 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1936: Prospectus, Draft #2 ("Showbook"): Working Papers, 198555 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1936: Names (Proposed), 198554 (Offsite-box 431)
  - Life: 1936: Names (Proposed) [RESTRICTED], 198553 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1936: Jan-May, 198552 (Offsite-box 431)
  - Life: 1936: Jan-May [RESTRICTED], 198551 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1936: June: Misc, 198550 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 21)
  - Life: 1936: July: Dummy #1 ("This is Dummy"), 198549 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1936: July: Prospectus, Draft #2 ("Showbook"): Originals of Final Version, 198548 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 23-24)
  - Life: 1936: July: Misc, 198547 (Offsite-box 431)